♪♪
Hey, baby, where are you going?
We've got a date, remember?
I've got to get home.
My son is sick.
Oh, now, why would
anybody care about that brat?
Unless, of course, you're
meeting somebody else.
No.
I think you're lying.
You are lying!
Leave her alone.
Okay.
Fine. No problem.
Just having a little
difference of opinion, that's all.
It's nothing for
you to worry about.
Aah!
He won't bother you again.
Will you, punk?
No.
No, I promise.
And I'll make sure
you keep that promise.
Now get out of here.
Okay.
Fine.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Jimmy.
Jimmy?
Yo, Jimmy.
Jimmy.
Hey, are you awake?
Hey, sport, run some cocktail
napkins out to Vern for me, will you?
My hands are kind of full.
They're over here on the box.
Okay.
Atta boy.
Thanks, champ.
You're a lifesaver.
♪♪
Put a lot of ice
in there, Lorraine.
Here you go, Vern.
It's about time. I got this one.
Get them tapped.
Here are the napkins, Vern.
How about you come
around and open them?
I need two drafts
and a Virgin Mary.
Coming right up.
Hi, Mom.
What are you doing back there?
He's helping me out.
Ellie went home sick,
and I'm shorthanded.
He's supposed to be sleeping.
Tomorrow's a school day.
Hey, you want him to
sleep, leave him home.
This is a honkytonk,
not a dormitory.
If you give me a raise
so I could pay a babysitter,
I'd be glad to leave him home.
But I like it here, Mom.
Don't worry, champ. It
will be a cold day in hell
before old Vern here
gives any of us a raise.
Here you go, Mom.
As soon as you're done,
back to the storeroom
and get some sleep.
Lorraine, darling,
can I get a beer?
Thank you.
Hey, doll, how are you doing?
- I'm doing just fine.
- Yes, you are. You're doing fine.
- What time do you get off?
- Not till closing.
All right. I'll be waiting.
What about her?
Darling, I'm just teaching
her the finer points of pinball.
That's all.
Hang on, Conrad! Hang on, baby!
Hey, Conrad, just
do it, Conrad! Do it!
Ride 'em!
All right!
Hey, what do you say, Ann?
You are really getting good.
Well, you think I ought
to be a rodeo rider?
I've been spending too
much time in this place.
No, it seems like you're
hardly ever here anymore.
Yeah, well, too busy, you know.
We miss you.
Thank you.
- I've got to get.
- All right. See you.
Hey, Hattie!
Come on, buddy,
let's get you home.
- Good night, you two.
- Good night, Walt.
Come on.
Good night, everybody.
- Good night.
Hey. Are you going my way?
No. I don't think so.
You know, you've
had an attitude all night.
I'm surprised you noticed.
What are you talking about?
Us, Dwayne.
You don't really care,
I don't really care.
So why don't we just get on
with our lives and call it quits?
That's it? It's
over, just like that?
You can come by tomorrow
morning at 11:00 and pick up your stuff.
I'll arrange to be out.
Come on, honey.
Hey, don't I get a
say in any of this?
There is nothing between
us, Dwayne, and you know it.
I think there is, and it ain't
over until I say it's over.
Understand? Don't think
you're getting in that car.
Let go of me.
Get off me, you
little... Let go of me.
Jimmy, stand back.
Stay away from us,
Dwayne. I mean it.
Do it, Mom. Get him.
Baby, what are you
going to do with that?
Dwayne.
Come on, come on.
Leave me alone.
Hey!
- Get off me.
- Leave him alone.
Come on.
- Ohh!
- Waste him, Walt! Waste him!
Aah!
Apologize to the lady.
- I said apologize.
- All right. All right!
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
You pick up your stuff tomorrow,
or it will be out on the street.
And don't you ever lay a
hand on me or my son again.
What the...?
Aah!
Geez.
Mrs. Johnson?
Dwayne?
He...
Why is it every time
I get a little time off
to do a few things around the
house like change a few light bulbs,
somebody I know
has a friend in trouble?
Ben, you've got to defend
her. She's such a nice person.
You said she's a waitress?
It's the only job she could get.
You know, the tips, and
she's got this little boy.
Well, how about
a public defender?
Ben, you've got to defend her.
Look, you'll see.
Ann Johnson is one of the
nicest, most hardworking,
honest, and courageous
people I've ever met.
Well, hell, Conrad,
instead of defending her,
why don't I just nominate
her for president?
Heh heh heh. You
character. Come on.
Ann?
Ann, I want you to
meet Ben Matlock,
probably the best
lawyer there ever was...
And a real nice man.
Ben, Ann Johnson.
- Hello.
Well, why don't we all sit down?
Okay.
Uh...
Well, what was...
What was this fellow's name?
Dwayne Meeks.
He was a real jerk.
Were you living with him?
Oh, not really.
He'd stay over every once
in a while... Often enough.
His stuff was
starting to pile up.
Is that what he was doing there
that morning? Getting his stuff?
Yeah.
Let's see, um...
you said that the police found
two little burn marks on his neck?
Yeah, remember? They
think before he was murdered,
he was stung with
one of those stun guns.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
A lot of people carry
those for defense.
Do you carry one?
I used to.
Dwayne knocked it out of my
hand when I had that fight with him.
Well, it's probably still
out there in the parking lot.
Uh, how many people
saw you out there that night?
Everybody who worked
till closing, I guess.
They probably thought I
was getting what I deserved
for having the worst taste in
men of any woman in history.
Yeah, she has had bad luck.
And like I said, that
Dwayne... He was a jerk.
You show me a self-centered,
mean-spirited jackass,
and chances are I've either
dated him or married him.
Well, hey, that boy of yours,
he's a hell of an artist, huh?
Oh, Jimmy's been drawing
ever since he could hold a pencil.
Of course, a lot of that is because I've
had to leave him on his own so much.
He got good at drawing because there
just plain wasn't anything else to do.
Yeah, but he got good at it.
Where is he now?
At Walt Thomas'.
He's a friend.
He works at Vern's, too.
You know, the worst thing about
being in here is being without Jimmy.
My arms ache,
they feel so empty.
How does it feel to have
murderer for a mom, Johnson?
She's not a murderer.
She's innocent.
She's in jail, isn't she?
Yeah. She's going
to go to the chair,
and you're going to
wind up in the orphanage
with all of the other
murderers' kids.
Shut up.
Who's going to make us? You?
I am, if I have to.
It's Mr. Awesome!
Let's get out of here!
Everything's going
to be all right, Jimmy.
Jimmy?
- Can I come in?
- Sure.
Lights out, champ. You've
got school tomorrow.
Hey, what have you got there?
Are you making a comic book?
That's great.
Mr. Awesome.
That's me.
Come on.
- Let's go to bed.
- Right.
Atta boy.
Slap me five.
You've got it.
Zap.
- Good night, champ.
- Good night.
I don't believe it.
Not Mrs. Johnson.
She's a model tenant.
She's always on time with the
rent, never plays her stereo too loud.
Of course, she doesn't have one.
Every penny she's got
goes to her boy's education.
She's got a lot of
character, that lady.
Yeah.
Did you notice anybody
else coming or going that day?
Just Dwayne.
He drove up while I was
out mowing the front yard.
I said hi. He just
walked right on past.
The guy was a jerk.
What she saw in
him is beyond me.
I guess she figured the boy
needed a father figure or something.
He needs a shrink,
if you ask me.
He's always up there
on the roof drawing.
- On the roof?
- Yeah.
He's got a little
clubhouse up there.
He made it out of little
scraps of wood I give him.
I thought a taste of
carpentry might get
him interested in, you
know, manly pursuits.
- Hey, Ben.
- Hmm?
Over here.
This lock's broken.
Yeah. That was
in the police report.
Ann said it's broken
most of the time.
Now wait a minute.
Every time she tells me
it's broken, I fix it right away.
I wanted to replace
it with a new one,
but the owner's the
biggest tightwad in Atlanta.
The guy makes a half a million
a year, and he still clips coupons.
Can you believe that?
Do you think the person that
killed Dwayne came in the back?
According to him, Dwayne
had a key to the front door,
and the back lock
was pretty flimsy.
Hey, did Jimmy do these?
Boy.
They're not bad for
an 11-year-old, huh?
No. He must be
some kind of genius.
He's smart. Look at that.
Those are the people
from Vern's Cowboy Palace.
Huh.
That's Lorraine Ortega...
she's a bartender.
That's the owner, Vern Trudeau.
That's Walt Thomas. That's
the guy Jimmy's staying with.
That's Ann.
And that's Dwayne Meeks.
He looks mean.
He was.
I guess that's the
way Jimmy saw him.
Yeah.
Boy, this kid's into violence.
Look at all this
fighting and zapping.
Look at that.
All little boys
draw stuff like that.
I guess.
I guess so.
♪♪
Hey, you see the little
filly there in tight jeans?
She's got quite a hitch
in her git-along, huh?
Hold on, hold on.
Hey!
Hang on, son, hang on, hang on.
I'm all right. I'm all right.
What's the matter with you?
You distracted me.
I'm actually very good at this.
At what? Flying through the
air and landing on your head?
No, at riding that thing. I
do it every time I come here.
- Why?
- It's fun, Ben.
You ought to try it some time.
You're nuts, you know that?
Hey, let's just
talk a little bit.
You don't pay money
to do that, do you?
Let's drop it.
Did you talk to the owner?
Yeah.
Nobody found a stun
gun in the parking lot.
Hey, Conrad.
Hey, Lorraine.
Would you like something?
No, not now.
Who is your good-looking friend?
Here's your hat.
Oh, I'm Ben
Matlock... Ann's lawyer.
Are you going to be
able to get her off?
I hope so.
Dwayne had it
coming, that's for sure.
I hear you used
to go out with him.
Me and half the women here.
Went through us one by one.
The big stud servicing his herd.
When did you break up?
- About a month ago.
- Oh.
Whose idea was it?
Mine.
How did he take it?
Well, within a week, he
was shacking up with Ann.
How did you take that?
No skin off my hide.
I wasn't his first, and Ann
wouldn't have been his last.
That morning that Dwayne
died... What was it, about 11?
- Yeah, about 11.
- 11. Uh, do you remember what...
In bed, sleeping in and
rediscovering the joys of celibacy.
Is Walt working tonight?
He's supposed to be.
Unless, of course, he's home
washing his socks and undies
- or reading a story to Jimmy.
- Lorraine!
Keep your pants on,
sugar, I'll be right there.
Excuse me.
Thanks, Lorraine.
I told you this would
happen, didn't I?
- Didn't I?
- Yeah. Yeah.
All right, listen up.
If I have to, next time
I'll break something.
And if you talk,
you're dead meat.
- You got that?
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's called a ten step.
I bet I could do that.
Maybe I'll do it with her.
There's Walt. Come on.
Hey, Walt.
Hey, Conrad. How are you doing?
All right.
Walt Thomas, meet Ben Matlock.
- Nice to meet you.
- How you doing?
How's Ann holding up?
Pretty well. Pretty well.
Your having Jimmy here with you
sure takes a load off her
shoulders, I'll tell you that.
Oh, it's no problem.
He's a great kid.
So what's going
to happen to her?
Well, it all depends on
whether I can find out
what really happened
to Dwayne Meeks.
Did you know him very well?
Yeah, he came in here
just about every night.
A lot of people
said he was a jerk.
- Yeah.
- He was a ladies' man, huh?
Oh, the ladies liked him
all right, including Ann.
I don't know why.
Then again, I'm no expert
when it comes to women.
Yeah, well, who is, yeah?
You didn't approve
of him and Ann, huh?
Well, let's just say I think she
could have done a whole lot better.
Yo, Walt, get up here
quick. I need your help.
One of the speakers went out.
Yeah, just a minute.
Is Jimmy here tonight?
Yeah, he's in the storeroom.
That's the first room on
your left, past the men's john.
- Okay.
- He's doing his homework.
- Yeah.
- Take care.
All right.
Uh, just wait.
Hey, Jimmy, I'm Ben
Matlock, your mother's lawyer.
Could I speak with
you for a minute?
Yeah.
Oh, don't put it away. I'd
like to see what you're doing.
Do you mind?
Are you going to make fun of me?
No.
The stuff I saw over at
your mom's house was great.
I may ask you for your autograph,
but I'd never make fun of you.
Oh, boy, you've got your
own comic book going here.
Boy, that Mr. Awesome looks a
lot like Walt Thomas, doesn't he?
Does he have super powers?
Yeah. He can transmit
psychically generated energy
through his central
nervous system
and out his fingertips by
reversing his sensory receptors.
Tssszz!
He can zap people.
Oh.
Oh, boy, that would be nice to
have super powers, wouldn't it?
I've always wished I
could fly like Superman.
Just put my arms out and just
jump and fly anywhere I wanted to.
Yeah. I'd like to have super strength
so I could beat up all the bad guys.
- You would?
- Yeah.
And I'd be invulnerable, too,
so they could hit me all they
wanted and they could never hurt me.
Did Dwayne Meeks ever hit you?
He threw me down
in the parking lot once.
You didn't like him
very much, did you?
I hated him.
Oh.
- Ben?
- Yeah.
I made some tuna
salad. Get some bread.
No, thanks.
There's hotdogs
and bologna and stuff.
Not hungry.
You're not?
I had this sort of
feeling about Jimmy.
What?
I went to his school, and
I talked to his principal.
Yeah?
He wasn't in class
the day of the murder.
Here it is.
The Taj Mahal she ain't, but then
again, Paul Bunyan Jimmy ain't.
You should have seen him.
He could barely lift that saw,
let alone swing that hammer.
Yeah, needs a
father, that's for sure.
A father and about
five years of shop class.
Do they teach shop
in school anymore?
Probably not.
I've got to get back to work.
If you need me, I'll be in 2B.
The toilet just
won't stop flushing.
Hello, Jimmy.
Hi, Mr. Matlock.
- I'll meet you guys downstairs.
- Okay.
So, uh, how was school?
- Fine.
- Mm-hmm.
I talked to your
principal the other day.
He said you don't
always make it to school.
Is that right?
Yeah.
He said you weren't there
the morning Dwayne died.
Where were you? Up here?
I found the stun gun.
What did you do with it?
I took it to the police.
Why did you do that?
What if they find
fingerprints or something?
Whose fingerprints are you afraid
they'll find on it, Jimmy? Yours?
No.
Whose, then?
I know you were up here that
day, Jimmy. Tell me what happened.
I was afraid that Dwayne
might hurt Mom again,
so I hid up here instead of going
to school and kind of kept watch.
Mom was still gone
by the time he got here,
so I just came up and
messed around for a while.
But then I heard somebody
open the back door to our place,
so I tried to see who
it was, but I couldn't.
I went downstairs to go inside,
and while I was
unlocking the front door,
I could hear somebody
run out the back door.
So by the time I got inside, the
only person I saw was Dwayne,
and I could tell right
away that he was dead.
Where was the stun gun?
It was on the floor next to him.
Why did you pick it up?
Because...
Did you think your
mom had killed him?
No.
When I looked over,
her car was gone,
and she would have come
in the front door, not the back.
Who are you protecting, Jimmy?
Jimmy?
I don't want to talk anymore.
Well, sooner or later,
you're going to have to tell
the police what you just told me.
You let that be a lesson to you.
Lorraine.
Conrad.
I never knew you
could ride like that.
Well, hell, I didn't, either.
It looked like you were
born on one of them things.
It just goes to show, you
never know what you can do
till somebody bets you
300 bucks you can't.
Whoa, sugar bait. I
know you from someplace.
Your dreams, more than likely.
Waco, that's it.
You used to live in Waco, Texas.
Waco?
In your bad dreams, doll.
Hey, is Walt around?
Nope. He just got off.
- Tell me something?
- Sure.
How did he get
along with Dwayne?
Oh.
After Dwayne started sleeping up
there with Ann, what do you think?
See, Walt doesn't know
it, but he's got a problem.
What's that?
He's in love with Ann.
It's obvious to
everybody but him.
Dwayne knew it.
That night, after Walt beat
him up in the parking lot,
Dwayne went on and on to everybody
about how he was going to get her back,
how nobody was ever
going to have her but him.
You know, just
rubbing Walt's nose in it.
Ann never told me that.
It happened after she drove off.
I thought old Walt was going to
pop a blood vessel, he got so mad.
What can I get you?
Nothing. Nothing.
- Good ride.
- Thank you.
Now that I've got a kid around,
I always seem to be
about a half a length behind.
Yeah.
I don't know how
single parents do it.
It's given me a whole new
respect for Annie, that's for sure.
You're pretty fond of her.
Oh, yeah.
Were you a little jealous
when she took up with Dwayne?
I got no right to be jealous. She
can take up with whoever she wants.
Do you remember where you
were the morning he was killed?
You think I killed him?
Well, you had that fight
with him the night before.
Yeah. And if I wanted to kill him,
I'd have done it right then and there.
I certainly wouldn't
try to frame Annie for it.
Oh, maybe you didn't
mean to frame Ann.
Maybe you didn't
mean to kill Dwayne.
Maybe you just wanted
to have it out with him
and things went
a little too far.
Maybe you had the stun gun and
were going to give it back to Ann
and used it on Dwayne
without even thinking.
That's a bunch of bull.
Well, if you'll tell me where you were
that morning, maybe I'll quit slinging it.
I was with someone.
A woman?
Yeah.
A married woman.
I'm going to have
to have her name.
Tina. Tina Sadowski.
Tina...
Mrs. Sadowski?
My name's Conrad McMasters.
Thanks a lot for coming.
Could we make this quick, you
know, on account of my husband?
- He's been getting real suspicious lately.
- Sure. Sure.
Let's see, you and Walt have
been seeing each other for how long?
About six months...
I mean weeks... about six weeks.
Six weeks.
I already told you that.
How did you two meet?
- How did we meet?
- Uh-huh.
She came in here one
night with a bunch of ladies,
and I guess we
just started talking.
At the bar.
We just started
talking one night.
Where was your husband?
He was working.
What does he do?
He sells real estate.
Oh. What's his name again?
- Joe.
Joe.
And where do you and
Walt usually rendezvous?
At his place.
At a motel. Look, you're
kind of holding me up here.
Look, I really do
have to get going.
- Well, thank you for your time.
- Don't mention it.
Thanks for coming.
How are you doing, Al?
Hey, it can't be time already.
I'm afraid so. Mr. Newstead
wants his money.
I don't have it.
Al, you don't pay up this time,
then I've got to break something.
Look, just give me one more day,
okay? I'll have it tomorrow. I swear.
You know the rules, Al.
Here... 180 bucks.
Everything I've got. Take it.
You owe 250.
What do you want me to do? Do
you want me to pull it out of a hat?
I don't have it.
I'm sorry, Al.
Wait, wait. The left
one, okay? The left one,
so I can still play ball
with my kids, okay?
Please?
All right. I'll tell you what.
Give me what you've got,
and I'll throw in the extra 70.
- Thanks.
- I want it back in one week.
You screw up, and I'll
break both your arms.
You've got it. I swear.
What are you doing here?
Eavesdropping.
How much did you hear?
Everything.
When did a nice fellow like you
start breaking legs for loan sharks?
I bet on a few too
many horses last year.
I owe Eddie
Newstead five figures.
He's letting me work it off.
It's not something
I'm real proud of.
I've been following you ever
since it became apparent to me
that you and Tina were
not having an affair.
Tina's a friend.
She's not married.
She's just trying
to help me out.
So what were you really doing
the morning Dwayne was killed?
Breaking a man's collarbone.
He was $85 short on a payment.
Remember his name?
Yeah. Tom Blackburn.
I guess what I do on my spare time makes
adultery look downright noble, doesn't it?
Don't tell Jimmy
about this, huh?
He looks up to me.
Hell, I'm the hero in that comic
book he's always working on.
There's no reason he
needs to know, right?
No, I guess not.
Thank you.
I mean it, thanks.
Jimmy, I want you
to think real hard.
When you looked to see who was at
the back door, did you see anything at all?
I mean, like their clothes
or their hair or anything?
By the time I got to the
edge, they were already inside.
What about when you
unlocked the front door?
You said you heard footsteps.
What did their shoes sound like?
Were they like boots...
loud... Or sneakers... soft?
I don't remember.
Well, I guess you weren't
meant to be a private detective,
but I'll tell you one
thing... You sure can draw.
You've got an eye for detail.
I just draw what's there.
Yeah.
Do you know when you drew these?
I always put the
date on the back.
Hello.
Yeah.
Mr. Matlock, it's for you.
Huh.
- It's Conrad. He sounds excited.
- Yeah?
Yeah, Conrad.
Yeah, that's it.
That's it.
Thanks. Bye.
Ms. Ortega, did you know
the deceased, Dwayne Meeks?
Everybody at Vern's knew him.
You went out with him.
For a while, yeah.
We broke up.
When?
About a month before he died.
Did you live with him?
No.
No?
What about all these
checks you wrote to him?
See, here's one for 700,
and here's one for 300,
and here's one for 500.
And there's more.
Are you sure they weren't
house payments or something?
No.
Well, what were they for?
He... They were loans.
Loans?
But he never paid you back.
See, I subpoenaed his bank statements, too,
and all that money went from you to him.
See that? Never from him to you.
Not once.
How come?
How come, Ms. Ortega?
They weren't loans, were they?
They were blackmail
payments, weren't they?
Why would Dwayne
be blackmailing me?
Because he found
out who you really are.
Not Lorraine Ortega
from Memphis, Tennessee,
but Cissy Lockwood
from Amarillo, Texas...
The girl the West
Texas Rodeo Association
voted Cowgirl of the Year 1985.
See that?
Mr. Conrad
McMasters, over there,
got curious when he saw
you riding that mechanical bull,
and he overheard that cowboy
say he knew you from Waco.
So he did some investigating.
And sure enough, he found out
that you indeed were on the
rodeo circuit back in Texas.
Barrel racing, right?
And what does that have to do...
He also found out something else
that Dwayne probably found out...
That there's an outstanding
warrant for your arrest back in Texas.
You fell in with a pretty bad
dude about four years ago,
and the two of you robbed a gas
station, nearly killed the attendant.
And you drove
the car to get away.
I did not.
That's what the fellow told the
police when they caught up to him.
- He's lying.
- Nevertheless, you're a fugitive.
I imagine that's why you changed your
name when you moved here to Atlanta
and why you gave Dwayne all that
money so he wouldn't tell the authorities.
But when you realized the payments
were never going to stop, you killed him.
None of that is true.
You knew he would be at Ann's
house by himself that morning.
You already had the stun gun...
You picked it up probably off the pavement
where he knocked it out of Ann's hand.
You slipped in
through her back door.
You knew she had a bad lock because
she complained about it all the time.
You used the stun gun
to incapacitate Dwayne,
then you killed him
with a blow to the head.
- Your Honor...
- Objection.
This is pure,
unadulterated speculation.
This is not speculation,
Your Honor.
This is not speculation.
Look at all the
facts we have so far.
She changed her name to
start a new life here in Atlanta.
She was barrel racing champion,
Cowgirl of the Year... kept that secret.
She helped a guy rob a gas station,
almost murdering the attendant.
Drove the car to get away.
She's a fugitive.
All those are facts.
Don't you imagine there's more?
We know all you've
just said, Mr. Matlock.
Now get on with it, and it
better not be speculation.
All right.
How about this?
What about it?
This is pure,
unadulterated proof.
It better be.
Would you please tell the
judge and the court what this is?
It's a belt buckle.
Not just any belt buckle.
This is the belt
buckle they gave you
when you were voted American
Barrel Racing Champion in 1987.
Right?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
The police found it in your apartment
this morning... with a warrant, of course.
And the reason I subpoenaed it
was because of these drawings
done by Jimmy Johnson.
See?
Now, here's a picture
of you wearing the belt.
See there?
This is in July before you
started going with Dwayne.
See there?
Now, these two are pictures of
Dwayne wearing the belt buckle
just before you
broke up with him.
See there?
Yet the police found it in
your possession this morning.
How could that be?
Your Honor, these
are just drawings.
They're drawings by an
11-year-old kid, for crying out loud.
I've always had the buckle.
You sure this wasn't
a blackmail payment?
- No.
- A gift, maybe?
I won that belt buckle because I
used to be the best at something.
I'd have never given it to
somebody like Dwayne ever.
Then why was he wearing
it when he was killed?
He wasn't wearing it.
Oh, but he was.
Old Dwayne, as you know,
had quite a way with the girls.
And when Ann wouldn't
sleep with him that night,
he just went over to
Sally Redmond's house.
Slept with her.
She told me. Yeah.
She said that he was...
But anyway, he left there
the morning he was killed.
Sally's sitting right over there,
ready, willing, and proud to testify
that he was wearing
this belt buckle
when he left her house
and went to Ann's house.
She remembers specifically
because he bragged on it.
And yet, when the police found his
body, he wasn't wearing a belt at all.
We wondered about that.
You took it off him, didn't you?
After you killed him.
Because, like you say, this belt
buckle means more to you than anything,
and you weren't about to see
him with it for all eternity, were you?
Has the jury reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
We find the defendant
Ann Johnson...
not guilty.
Hey, that's me.
I call him Justice Man.
Got super powers, huh?
Yeah. He can generate
a force field around him
that only truth and
justice can penetrate.
Oh, my gosh, I almost forgot.
What's that?
It's a cape.
Why does he need a cape?
Because Justice Man can fly.
www.tvsubtitles.net